{
    "questions": [
        {
            "topic": "REST APIs",
            "id": 1,
            "question": "\"What type of relationship is defined as one resource existing only if another parent resource exist-for example, pages in a book?\"",
            "body": "",
            "answer": "\"`dependent`\"",
            "choices": [
                "`Partial`",
                "`dependent`",
                "`associative`",
                "`linked`"
            ]
        },
        {
            "topic": "REST APIs",
            "id": 2,
            "question": "\"Which URL pattern is recommended when working with one resource and a collection of resources?\"",
            "body": "",
            "answer": "\"`/companies/{id} and /companies`\"",
            "choices": [
                "`/companies/{id} and /company`",
                "`/company/{id} and /companies`",
                "`/companies/{id} and /companies`",
                "`/company/{id} and /company`"
            ]
        },
        {
            "topic": "REST APIs",
            "id": 3,
            "question": "\"When dealing with JSON web Tokens (JWTs), what is a claim?\"",
            "body": "",
            "answer": "\"`data in the token`\"",
            "choices": [
                "`data in the token`",
                "`Ownership`",
                "`a permission`",
                "`and integer`"
            ]
        },
        {
            "topic": "REST APIs",
            "id": 4,
            "question": "\"Which REST constraint specifies that knowledge and understanding obtained from one component of the API should be generally applicable elsewhere in the API?\"",
            "body": "",
            "answer": "\"`Uniform Interface`\"",
            "choices": [
                "`Uniform Interface`",
                "`Client-Server`",
                "`Stateless`",
                "`Chacheable`"
            ]
        },
        {
            "topic": "REST APIs",
            "id": 5,
            "question": "\"What would you enable to allow a browser on another site to make an AJAX request to your API?\"",
            "body": "",
            "answer": "\"`CORS`\"",
            "choices": [
                "`HTTP`",
                "`REST`",
                "`OPTIONS`",
                "`CORS`"
            ]
        },
        {
            "topic": "REST APIs",
            "id": 6,
            "question": "\"APIs commonly use webhooks to **\\_**.\"",
            "body": "",
            "answer": "\"`notify other systems of an event`\"",
            "choices": [
                "`notify other systems of an event`",
                "`catch error faster`",
                "`improve error logging`",
                "`log additional data`"
            ]
        },
        {
            "topic": "REST APIs",
            "id": 7,
            "question": "\"What is the underlying goal of all APIs?\"",
            "body": "",
            "answer": "\"`to share features and functionality with other system.`\"",
            "choices": [
                "`to add new technologies to an organization's infrastructure.`",
                "`to share features and functionality with other system.`",
                "`to move infrastructure to the cloud.`",
                "`to appease the latest digital transformation effort.`"
            ]
        },
        {
            "topic": "REST APIs",
            "id": 8,
            "question": "\"Which is a common command-line tool for using or exploring an API?\"",
            "body": "",
            "answer": "\"`curl`\"",
            "choices": [
                "`bash`",
                "`curl`",
                "`ssh`",
                "`powerShell`"
            ]
        },
        {
            "topic": "REST APIs",
            "id": 9,
            "question": "\"What is the modern specification for describing an API?\"",
            "body": "",
            "answer": "\"`OpenAPI (Swagger)`\"",
            "choices": [
                "`OpenAPI (Swagger)`",
                "`WADL`",
                "`WSDL`",
                "`OAuth`"
            ]
        },
        {
            "topic": "REST APIs",
            "id": 10,
            "question": "\"Which HTTP verb is normally used to update or create a resource in an API?\"",
            "body": "",
            "answer": "\"`POST`\"",
            "choices": [
                "`SUBMIT`",
                "`WRITE`",
                "`POST`",
                "`CREATE`"
            ]
        },
        {
            "topic": "REST APIs",
            "id": 11,
            "question": "\"What is one benefit of server-side caching in APIs?\"",
            "body": "",
            "answer": "\"`It reduce load on servers.`\"",
            "choices": [
                "`Mobile app work better.`",
                "`It improves uptime.`",
                "`It offers better security.`",
                "`It reduce load on servers.`"
            ]
        },
        {
            "topic": "REST APIs",
            "id": 12,
            "question": "\"Your API resource does no allow deletion, and a client application attempted to delete the resource. What HTTP response code should you return?\"",
            "body": "",
            "answer": "\"`405 Method Not Allowed`\"",
            "choices": [
                "`409 Conflict`",
                "`400 Bad Request`",
                "`406 Not Acceptable`",
                "`405 Method Not Allowed`"
            ]
        },
        {
            "topic": "REST APIs",
            "id": 13,
            "question": "\"What is OpenID Connect?\"",
            "body": "",
            "answer": "\"`an identify layer on top of OAuth 2.0`\"",
            "choices": [
                "`an identify layer on top of OAuth 2.0`",
                "`the new name for SAML 3.0`",
                "`a modern replacement for API keys`",
                "`an SSO competitor for OAuth 2.0`"
            ]
        },
        {
            "topic": "REST APIs",
            "id": 14,
            "question": "\"What is one benefit of GraphQl over REST approaches?\"",
            "body": "",
            "answer": "\"`flexible querying/responses`\"",
            "choices": [
                "`flexible querying/responses`",
                "`more stable APIs`",
                "`compatible with more gateways`",
                "`more secure by default`"
            ]
        },
        {
            "topic": "REST APIs",
            "id": 15,
            "question": "\"Which REST constraint specifies that there should be no shared context?\"",
            "body": "",
            "answer": "\"`Stateless`\"",
            "choices": [
                "`Stateless`",
                "`Client-Server`",
                "`Uniform Interface`",
                "`Cacheable`"
            ]
        },
        {
            "topic": "REST APIs",
            "id": 16,
            "question": "\"What purpose does a User-Agent serve?\"",
            "body": "",
            "answer": "\"`It identifies the client application or SDK.`\"",
            "choices": [
                "`It identifies the user ID.`",
                "`It identifies the client application or SDK.`",
                "`It identifies if the API should expect a user authentication.`",
                "`It identifies if the API should accept microservice traffic.`"
            ]
        },
        {
            "topic": "REST APIs",
            "id": 17,
            "question": "\"If you were to add versioning by using the Accept and Content-Type header, what would be the correct format of the header value?\"",
            "body": "",
            "answer": "\"`application/vnd.myapp.v2+json`\"",
            "choices": [
                "`application/json`",
                "`application/json_version2`",
                "`text/html`",
                "`application/vnd.myapp.v2+json`"
            ]
        },
        {
            "topic": "REST APIs",
            "id": 18,
            "question": "\"What is one benefit that OAuth provides over an API key approach?\"",
            "body": "",
            "answer": "\"`A token is scoped to the use case.`\"",
            "choices": [
                "`A token is encrypted.`",
                "`A token is encoded.`",
                "`A token is scoped to the use case.`",
                "`A token can be shared between systems.`"
            ]
        },
        {
            "topic": "REST APIs",
            "id": 19,
            "question": "\"The ability to execute the same API request over and over again without changing the resource's state is an example of \\_.\"",
            "body": "",
            "answer": "\"`idempotency`\"",
            "choices": [
                "`stateless architecture`",
                "`idempotency`",
                "`a uniform interface`",
                "`cacheability`"
            ]
        },
        {
            "topic": "REST APIs",
            "id": 20,
            "question": "\"What component can you use to wrap legacy architectures or protocols into a REST interface for easier consumption and integration?\"",
            "body": "",
            "answer": "\"`API proxy`\"",
            "choices": [
                "`API proxy`",
                "`API gateway`",
                "`OpenAPI`",
                "`OAuth authorization server`"
            ]
        },
        {
            "topic": "REST APIs",
            "id": 21,
            "question": "\"What protection does a JSON Web Token (JWT) offer to mitigate tampering with its contents?\"",
            "body": "",
            "answer": "\"`a signature`\"",
            "choices": [
                "`transport over SSL`",
                "`encrypted payload`",
                "`a signature`",
                "`encoded payload`"
            ]
        },
        {
            "topic": "REST APIs",
            "id": 22,
            "question": "\"What OAuth term is used to represent permissions?\"",
            "body": "",
            "answer": "\"`scope`\"",
            "choices": [
                "`token`",
                "`scope`",
                "`claim`",
                "`back channel`"
            ]
        },
        {
            "topic": "REST APIs",
            "id": 23,
            "question": "\"What additional type of token would you see when using OpenID Connect?\"",
            "body": "",
            "answer": "\"`ID token`\"",
            "choices": [
                "`ID token`",
                "`refresh token`",
                "`access token`",
                "`auth code token`"
            ]
        },
        {
            "topic": "REST APIs",
            "id": 24,
            "question": "\"What should you add to a Cache-Control response header to specify that a response should not be stored in an intermediary cache?\"",
            "body": "",
            "answer": "\"`private`\"",
            "choices": [
                "`no-proxy`",
                "`client-only`",
                "`restricted`",
                "`private`"
            ]
        },
        {
            "topic": "REST APIs",
            "id": 25,
            "question": "\"Which OAuth grant type can support a refresh token?\"",
            "body": "",
            "answer": "\"`Authorization Code Grant`\"",
            "choices": [
                "`Authorization Code Grant`",
                "`Client Credentials Grant`",
                "`Implicit Grant`",
                "`Authentication Grant`"
            ]
        },
        {
            "topic": "REST APIs",
            "id": 26,
            "question": "\"Using OAuth, what scope would you request for write access to the API?\"",
            "body": "",
            "answer": "\"`admin`\"",
            "choices": [
                "`It varies from API to API.`",
                "`admin`",
                "`write`",
                "`read-write`"
            ]
        },
        {
            "topic": "REST APIs",
            "id": 27,
            "question": "\"Which property would you use to include subresources directly into a JSON document?\"",
            "body": "",
            "answer": "\"`subresources`\"",
            "choices": [
                "`_embedded`",
                "`resources`",
                "`subresources`",
                "`_links`"
            ]
        },
        {
            "topic": "REST APIs",
            "id": 28,
            "question": "\"What is the best way to track SDK and version usage?\"",
            "body": "",
            "answer": "\"`tracking downloads`\"",
            "choices": [
                "`tracking downloads`",
                "`Accept headers`",
                "`user agents`",
                "`polling users`"
            ]
        },
        {
            "topic": "REST APIs",
            "id": 29,
            "question": "\"Which REST constraint allows for the presence of caching, routing, and other systems between the client and server?\"",
            "body": "",
            "answer": "\"`Layered System`\"",
            "choices": [
                "`Layered System`",
                "`Stateless`",
                "`Client-Server`",
                "`Cacheable`"
            ]
        },
        {
            "topic": "REST APIs",
            "id": 30,
            "question": "\"Which content is best to include in your documentation?\"",
            "body": "",
            "answer": "\"`sample code`\"",
            "choices": [
                "`your tech stack`",
                "`reasoning for your naming schema`",
                "`your mission statement`",
                "`sample code`"
            ]
        },
        {
            "topic": "REST APIs",
            "id": 31,
            "question": "\"What metric tracks overall availability for your API?\"",
            "body": "",
            "answer": "\"`Uptime`\"",
            "choices": [
                "`Response Time`",
                "`Time to First Hello World`",
                "`TTL`",
                "`Uptime`"
            ]
        },
        {
            "topic": "REST APIs",
            "id": 32,
            "question": "\"What is the recommended method and URL pattern for retrieving a specific user?\"",
            "body": "",
            "answer": "\"`GET /users/{id}`\"",
            "choices": [
                "`GET /user/{id}`",
                "`GET /users/{id}`",
                "`GET /user?id={id}`",
                "`GET /users?id={id}`"
            ]
        },
        {
            "topic": "REST APIs",
            "id": 33,
            "question": "\"What is the purpose of a link relation?\"",
            "body": "",
            "answer": "\"`to link two resources together`\"",
            "choices": [
                "`to describe relationships between resources or actions`",
                "`to describe subresources related to the current one`",
                "`to link two resources together`",
                "`to describe a resource and its purpose`"
            ]
        },
        {
            "topic": "REST APIs",
            "id": 34,
            "question": "\"When building SDKs, which languages should you support?\"",
            "body": "",
            "answer": "\"the languages that your target users use\"",
            "choices": [
                "Java, Javascript, and .NET",
                "and you can support",
                "PHP, Python, and Go",
                "the languages that your target users use"
            ]
        },
        {
            "topic": "REST APIs",
            "id": 35,
            "question": "\"Which property would you use to include references to other resources in a JSON document?\"",
            "body": "",
            "answer": "\"`resources`\"",
            "choices": [
                "`resources`",
                "`_embedded`",
                "`subresources`",
                "`_links`"
            ]
        },
        {
            "topic": "REST APIs",
            "id": 36,
            "question": "\"What is OAuth?\"",
            "body": "",
            "answer": "\"an authorization framework for granted delegated access\"",
            "choices": [
                "an authorization framework for granted delegated access",
                "an approach to single sign-on for APIs",
                "a method for API authentication",
                "HTTP Basic Authentication 2.0"
            ]
        },
        {
            "topic": "REST APIs",
            "id": 37,
            "question": "\"What should your API documentation describe?\"",
            "body": "",
            "answer": "\"common use cases\"",
            "choices": [
                "JSON",
                "HTTP",
                "common use cases",
                "your tech stack"
            ]
        },
        {
            "topic": "REST APIs",
            "id": 38,
            "question": "\"What is the purpose of an OAuth refresh token?\"",
            "body": "",
            "answer": "\"to retrieve an access token\"",
            "choices": [
                "to share user profile information",
                "to update an API configuration",
                "to keep a web session active",
                "to retrieve an access token"
            ]
        },
        {
            "topic": "REST APIs",
            "id": 39,
            "question": "\"What is Time to First Hello World?\"",
            "body": "",
            "answer": "\"how long it takes for a developer to do something with your API\"",
            "choices": [
                "how long it takes for a developer to do something with your API",
                "how long it takes to start a new programming language",
                "how long it takes to install your SDK",
                "how long it takes to read your documentation"
            ]
        },
        {
            "topic": "REST APIs",
            "id": 40,
            "question": "\"Which response header tells the client and intermediaries that the response is not to be cached anywhere?\"",
            "body": "",
            "answer": "\"Cache-Control: no-store\"",
            "choices": [
                "Cache-State: none",
                "Expires:-1",
                "Cache-Control: no-cache",
                "Cache-Control: no-store"
            ]
        },
        {
            "topic": "REST APIs",
            "id": 41,
            "question": "\"What component hides the distinctions or boundaries between various microservices from end-client applications?\"",
            "body": "",
            "answer": "\"`API gateway`\"",
            "choices": [
                "`API gateway`",
                "`API logging `",
                "`a layered system `",
                "`API proxy`"
            ]
        },
        {
            "topic": "REST APIs",
            "id": 42,
            "question": "\"The textbook approach to api versioning is to use **\\_**.\"",
            "body": "",
            "answer": "\"`the Accept header`\"",
            "choices": [
                "`common knowledge`",
                "`URLs`",
                "`no versioning`",
                "`the Accept header`"
            ]
        },
        {
            "topic": "REST APIs",
            "id": 43,
            "question": "\"Which is the most secure method to transmit an API key?\"",
            "body": "",
            "answer": "\"`Authorization header`\"",
            "choices": [
                "`URL parameter`",
                "`Authorization header`",
                "`Base64 encoding`",
                "`Basic Auth`"
            ]
        },
        {
            "topic": "REST APIs",
            "id": 44,
            "question": "\"Within Oauth, what component validates the user's identity?\"",
            "body": "",
            "answer": "\"`authorization server`\"",
            "choices": [
                "`client`",
                "`not specified`",
                "`authorization server`",
                "`resource server`"
            ]
        },
        {
            "topic": "REST APIs",
            "id": 45,
            "question": "\"API traffic that is entirely internal to your organization is normally called \\_?\"",
            "body": "",
            "answer": "\"`internal traffic `\"",
            "choices": [
                "`inbound traffic`",
                "`north-south traffic `",
                "`internal traffic `",
                "`east-west traffic`"
            ]
        },
        {
            "topic": "REST APIs",
            "id": 46,
            "question": "\"What is the best approach for requesting JSON instead of XML from an API?\"",
            "body": "",
            "answer": "\"`Use the Accept header.`\"",
            "choices": [
                "`Add .json to the URL.`",
                "`APIs do not use XML.`",
                "`Use the Content-Type header.`",
                "`Use the Accept header.`"
            ]
        },
        {
            "topic": "REST APIs",
            "id": 47,
            "question": "\"When a user attempts to access a record that is not their own, which HTTP response code is the most appropriate?\"",
            "body": "",
            "answer": "\"`403`\"",
            "choices": [
                "`403`",
                "`404`",
                "`401`",
                "`405`"
            ]
        },
        {
            "topic": "REST APIs",
            "id": 48,
            "question": "\"Which is a benefit of using an API gateway?\"",
            "body": "",
            "answer": "\"`rate limiting/throttling`\"",
            "choices": [
                "`HTTP verbs`",
                "`JSON payloads`",
                "`HTTP response codes`",
                "`rate limiting/throttling`"
            ]
        },
        {
            "topic": "REST APIs",
            "id": 49,
            "question": "\"API testing must be treated as **\\_**?\"",
            "body": "",
            "answer": "\"`black box testing`\"",
            "choices": [
                "`red team testing`",
                "`white box testing`",
                "`blue box testing`",
                "`black box testing`"
            ]
        },
        {
            "topic": "REST APIs",
            "id": 50,
            "question": "\"Which HTTP verb is used in a CORS preflight request?\"",
            "body": "",
            "answer": "\"`OPTIONS`\"",
            "choices": [
                "`PUT`",
                "`POST`",
                "`GET`",
                "`OPTIONS`"
            ]
        },
        {
            "topic": "REST APIs",
            "id": 51,
            "question": "\"Which response header will tell the client that the response is cached for 1 minute ?\"",
            "body": "",
            "answer": "\"`Cache-Control: max-age=60`\"",
            "choices": [
                "`Expires: 1 minute`",
                "`Cache-Control: max-age=60`",
                "`Expires: 1 January 2020`",
                "`Cache-Expires: max-age=60`"
            ]
        },
        {
            "topic": "REST APIs",
            "id": 52,
            "question": "\"What is the concept that allows an API client to explore an API via links embedded in payloads?\"",
            "body": "",
            "answer": "\"`link relations`\"",
            "choices": [
                "`hypermedia`",
                "`link relations`",
                "`parsing`",
                "`browsing`"
            ]
        },
        {
            "topic": "REST APIs",
            "id": 53,
            "question": "\"To create a new resource, what HTTP response code should you receive?\"",
            "body": "",
            "answer": "\"`201`\"",
            "choices": [
                "`405`",
                "`201`",
                "`204`",
                "`202`"
            ]
        },
        {
            "topic": "REST APIs",
            "id": 54,
            "question": "\"Which is an example of Code on Demand?\"",
            "body": "",
            "answer": "\"JavaScript on a webpage\"",
            "choices": [
                "AWS Lambda",
                "downloading open-source software",
                "Serverless",
                "JavaScript on a webpage"
            ]
        },
        {
            "topic": "REST APIs",
            "id": 55,
            "question": "\"Which URL pattern should you follow for accessing a subresource attached to a specific resource?\"",
            "body": "",
            "answer": "\"/companies/{companyId}/employees/{employeeId}\"",
            "choices": [
                "/companies/employees/{companyId}/{employeeId}",
                "/company/{companyId}/employees/{employeeId}",
                "/companies/{companyId}/employees/{employeeId}",
                "/companies/{companyId}/employee/{employeeId}"
            ]
        },
        {
            "topic": "REST APIs",
            "id": 56,
            "question": "\"Which REST constraint essentially prohibits the use of cookies?\"",
            "body": "",
            "answer": "\"Stateless\"",
            "choices": [
                "Stateless",
                "Cacheable",
                "Layered System",
                "Uniform Interface"
            ]
        },
        {
            "topic": "REST APIs",
            "id": 57,
            "question": "\"Which HTTP verb is used to delete a resource?\"",
            "body": "",
            "answer": "\"DELETE\"",
            "choices": [
                "FLUSH",
                "DELETE",
                "CLEAR",
                "DESTROY"
            ]
        },
        {
            "topic": "REST APIs",
            "id": 58,
            "question": "\"Which verb is _not_ considered idempotent?\"",
            "body": "",
            "answer": "\"POST\"",
            "choices": [
                "DELETE",
                "GET",
                "PUT",
                "POST"
            ]
        },
        {
            "topic": "REST APIs",
            "id": 59,
            "question": "\"Which REST constraint specifies that each request should stand on its own and not have a specific required order?\"",
            "body": "",
            "answer": "\"Stateless\"",
            "choices": [
                "Uniform Interface",
                "Cacheable",
                "Stateless",
                "Client-Server"
            ]
        },
        {
            "topic": "REST APIs",
            "id": 60,
            "question": "\"When you get a 429 response code, what should you do next?\"",
            "body": "",
            "answer": "\"Slow down your requests.\"",
            "choices": [
                "Check you JSON structure.",
                "Slow down your requests.",
                "Check the API uptime status.",
                "Check you API key."
            ]
        },
        {
            "topic": "REST APIs",
            "id": 61,
            "question": "\"When exploring record sets, what is the best approach for pagination?\"",
            "body": "",
            "answer": "\"next/previous cursors\"",
            "choices": [
                "date-based filtering",
                "next/previous cursors",
                "page size and filters",
                "database IDs"
            ]
        },
        {
            "topic": "REST APIs",
            "id": 62,
            "question": "\"What is _not_ a method for API authentication or authorization?\"",
            "body": "",
            "answer": "\"biometrics\"",
            "choices": [
                "OAuth",
                "biometrics",
                "API Keys",
                "username and password"
            ]
        },
        {
            "topic": "REST APIs",
            "id": 63,
            "question": "\"Which HTTP response code usually means the requested work is still processing and may or may not result in an error later?\"",
            "body": "",
            "answer": "\"202 Accepted\"",
            "choices": [
                "200 OK",
                "204 No Content",
                "201 Created",
                "202 Accepted"
            ]
        },
        {
            "topic": "REST APIs",
            "id": 64,
            "question": "\"When validating a JWT, what are some of the claims that you must confirm? (Select all that apply.)\"",
            "body": "A. The exp (expiration) has not passed.\n    B. The algorithm is sufficient.\n    C. The signature matches the payload.\n    D. The token was Base64 encoded.\n    E. The iss (issuer) is the auth server you expect.\n    F. There is a refresh token.\n    G. The cid (client ID) is the client you expect.\n    H. The token was encrypted.",
            "answer": "\"A,B,E,H\"",
            "choices": [
                "A,B,E,H",
                "B,C,F,G",
                "A,D,G,H",
                "A,C,E,G"
            ]
        },
        {
            "topic": "REST APIs",
            "id": 65,
            "question": "\"API traffic that enters and leaves your organization is normally called **\\_**?\"",
            "body": "",
            "answer": "\"`north-south traffic`\"",
            "choices": [
                "`east-west traffic`",
                "`inbound traffic`",
                "`north-south traffic`",
                "`external traffic`"
            ]
        },
        {
            "topic": "REST APIs",
            "id": 66,
            "question": "\"Which OAuth grant type is appropriate for mobile apps?\"",
            "body": "",
            "answer": "\"Authorization Code with PKCE\"",
            "choices": [
                "Authorization Code with PKCE",
                "Client Credentials",
                "Device",
                "Resource Owner Password"
            ]
        },
        {
            "topic": "REST APIs",
            "id": 67,
            "question": "\"Which datetime format is the easiest or most predictable to parse and process?\"",
            "body": "",
            "answer": "\"`YYYY-MM-DDThh:mm:ssZ`\"",
            "choices": [
                "`YY-M-D hh:mm:ss+TZ`",
                "`YY-M-D h:mm:ss`",
                "`YYYY-MM-DDThh:mm:ssZ`",
                "`YYYY-M-D hh:mm:ss`"
            ]
        },
        {
            "topic": "REST APIs",
            "id": 68,
            "question": "\"Which header is _not_ used in cache management?\"",
            "body": "",
            "answer": "\"Rate-Limit\"",
            "choices": [
                "Rate-Limit",
                "Expires",
                "Etag",
                "Cache-Control"
            ]
        },
        {
            "topic": "REST APIs",
            "id": 69,
            "question": "\"A client application uses a filter or a search in your API correctly but there are zero results. What is the best response code?\"",
            "body": "",
            "answer": "\"200 OK\"",
            "choices": [
                "204 No Content",
                "400 Bad Request",
                "200 OK",
                "404 Not Found"
            ]
        }
    ]
}